{
  "shapes": [
    {
      "id": "1",
      "name": "",
      "type": "Shape",
      "text": "Box 1",
      "master": "2",
      "geometry": {
        "BeginX": null,
        "BeginY": null,
        "EndX": null,
        "EndY": null
      },
      "line_format": {
        "LineColor": null,
        "LineWeight": "0.01041666666666667",
        "EndArrow": null
      },
      "master_nameU": "Rectangle",
      "master_name": "Rectangle",
      "master_prompt": "Drag onto the page.",
      "master_contents": {
        "shape_id": "5",
        "type": "Shape",
        "line_style": "7",
        "fill_style": "7",
        "text_style": "7",
        "cells": {
          "PinX": "1.5",
          "PinY": "1.5",
          "Width": "1",
          "Height": "-1",
          "LocPinX": "0.5",
          "LocPinY": "-0.5",
          "Angle": "0",
          "FlipX": "0",
          "FlipY": "0",
          "ResizeMode": "0",
          "BeginX": "1",
          "BeginY": "2",
          "EndX": "2",
          "EndY": "1",
          "TxtPinX": "0",
          "TxtPinY": "-1",
          "TxtWidth": "0.5555555555555556",
          "TxtHeight": "0.2444444444444444",
          "TxtLocPinX": "0.2777777777777778",
          "TxtLocPinY": "0.1222222222222222",
          "TxtAngle": "0",
          "LockHeight": "1",
          "LockCalcWH": "1",
          "HelpTopic": "Vis_SE.chm!#20000",
          "Copyright": "Copyright 2001 Microsoft Corporation.  All rights reserved.",
          "NoAlignBox": "1",
          "DynFeedback": "2",
          "GlueType": "2",
          "ObjType": "2",
          "NoLiveDynamics": "1",
          "ShapeSplittable": "1",
          "LayerMember": "0"
        },
        "sections": [
          {
            "name": "Control",
            "rows": [
              {
                "N": "TextPosition",
                "cells": {
                  "X": "0",
                  "Y": "-1",
                  "XDyn": "0",
                  "YDyn": "-1",
                  "XCon": "5",
                  "YCon": "0",
                  "CanGlue": "0",
                  "Prompt": "Reposition Text"
                }
              }
            ]
          },
          {
            "name": "Geometry",
            "rows": [
              {
                "T": "MoveTo",
                "IX": "1",
                "cells": {
                  "X": "0",
                  "Y": "0"
                }
              },
              {
                "T": "LineTo",
                "IX": "2",
                "cells": {
                  "X": "0",
                  "Y": "-1"
                }
              },
              {
                "T": "LineTo",
                "IX": "3",
                "cells": {
                  "X": "1",
                  "Y": "-1"
                }
              }
            ]
          }
        ]
      },
      "is_connector": false
    },
    {
      "id": "2",
      "name": "Rectangle.2",
      "type": "Shape",
      "text": "Box 2",
      "master": "2",
      "geometry": {
        "BeginX": null,
        "BeginY": null,
        "EndX": null,
        "EndY": null
      },
      "line_format": {
        "LineColor": null,
        "LineWeight": "0.01041666666666667",
        "EndArrow": null
      },
      "master_nameU": "Rectangle",
      "master_name": "Rectangle",
      "master_prompt": "Drag onto the page.",
      "master_contents": {
        "shape_id": "5",
        "type": "Shape",
        "line_style": "7",
        "fill_style": "7",
        "text_style": "7",
        "cells": {
          "PinX": "1.5",
          "PinY": "1.5",
          "Width": "1",
          "Height": "-1",
          "LocPinX": "0.5",
          "LocPinY": "-0.5",
          "Angle": "0",
          "FlipX": "0",
          "FlipY": "0",
          "ResizeMode": "0",
          "BeginX": "1",
          "BeginY": "2",
          "EndX": "2",
          "EndY": "1",
          "TxtPinX": "0",
          "TxtPinY": "-1",
          "TxtWidth": "0.5555555555555556",
          "TxtHeight": "0.2444444444444444",
          "TxtLocPinX": "0.2777777777777778",
          "TxtLocPinY": "0.1222222222222222",
          "TxtAngle": "0",
          "LockHeight": "1",
          "LockCalcWH": "1",
          "HelpTopic": "Vis_SE.chm!#20000",
          "Copyright": "Copyright 2001 Microsoft Corporation.  All rights reserved.",
          "NoAlignBox": "1",
          "DynFeedback": "2",
          "GlueType": "2",
          "ObjType": "2",
          "NoLiveDynamics": "1",
          "ShapeSplittable": "1",
          "LayerMember": "0"
        },
        "sections": [
          {
            "name": "Control",
            "rows": [
              {
                "N": "TextPosition",
                "cells": {
                  "X": "0",
                  "Y": "-1",
                  "XDyn": "0",
                  "YDyn": "-1",
                  "XCon": "5",
                  "YCon": "0",
                  "CanGlue": "0",
                  "Prompt": "Reposition Text"
                }
              }
            ]
          },
          {
            "name": "Geometry",
            "rows": [
              {
                "T": "MoveTo",
                "IX": "1",
                "cells": {
                  "X": "0",
                  "Y": "0"
                }
              },
              {
                "T": "LineTo",
                "IX": "2",
                "cells": {
                  "X": "0",
                  "Y": "-1"
                }
              },
              {
                "T": "LineTo",
                "IX": "3",
                "cells": {
                  "X": "1",
                  "Y": "-1"
                }
              }
            ]
          }
        ]
      },
      "is_connector": false
    },
    {
      "id": "4",
      "name": "",
      "type": "Shape",
      "text": "Box 3",
      "master": "2",
      "geometry": {
        "BeginX": null,
        "BeginY": null,
        "EndX": null,
        "EndY": null
      },
      "line_format": {
        "LineColor": null,
        "LineWeight": "0.01041666666666667",
        "EndArrow": null
      },
      "master_nameU": "Rectangle",
      "master_name": "Rectangle",
      "master_prompt": "Drag onto the page.",
      "master_contents": {
        "shape_id": "5",
        "type": "Shape",
        "line_style": "7",
        "fill_style": "7",
        "text_style": "7",
        "cells": {
          "PinX": "1.5",
          "PinY": "1.5",
          "Width": "1",
          "Height": "-1",
          "LocPinX": "0.5",
          "LocPinY": "-0.5",
          "Angle": "0",
          "FlipX": "0",
          "FlipY": "0",
          "ResizeMode": "0",
          "BeginX": "1",
          "BeginY": "2",
          "EndX": "2",
          "EndY": "1",
          "TxtPinX": "0",
          "TxtPinY": "-1",
          "TxtWidth": "0.5555555555555556",
          "TxtHeight": "0.2444444444444444",
          "TxtLocPinX": "0.2777777777777778",
          "TxtLocPinY": "0.1222222222222222",
          "TxtAngle": "0",
          "LockHeight": "1",
          "LockCalcWH": "1",
          "HelpTopic": "Vis_SE.chm!#20000",
          "Copyright": "Copyright 2001 Microsoft Corporation.  All rights reserved.",
          "NoAlignBox": "1",
          "DynFeedback": "2",
          "GlueType": "2",
          "ObjType": "2",
          "NoLiveDynamics": "1",
          "ShapeSplittable": "1",
          "LayerMember": "0"
        },
        "sections": [
          {
            "name": "Control",
            "rows": [
              {
                "N": "TextPosition",
                "cells": {
                  "X": "0",
                  "Y": "-1",
                  "XDyn": "0",
                  "YDyn": "-1",
                  "XCon": "5",
                  "YCon": "0",
                  "CanGlue": "0",
                  "Prompt": "Reposition Text"
                }
              }
            ]
          },
          {
            "name": "Geometry",
            "rows": [
              {
                "T": "MoveTo",
                "IX": "1",
                "cells": {
                  "X": "0",
                  "Y": "0"
                }
              },
              {
                "T": "LineTo",
                "IX": "2",
                "cells": {
                  "X": "0",
                  "Y": "-1"
                }
              },
              {
                "T": "LineTo",
                "IX": "3",
                "cells": {
                  "X": "1",
                  "Y": "-1"
                }
              }
            ]
          }
        ]
      },
      "is_connector": false
    },
    {
      "id": "6",
      "name": "",
      "type": "Shape",
      "text": "Box 4",
      "master": "7",
      "geometry": {
        "BeginX": null,
        "BeginY": null,
        "EndX": null,
        "EndY": null
      },
      "line_format": {
        "LineColor": null,
        "LineWeight": "0.01041666666666667",
        "EndArrow": null
      },
      "master_nameU": "Circle",
      "master_name": "Circle",
      "master_prompt": "Drag onto the page.",
      "master_contents": {},
      "is_connector": false
    },
    {
      "id": "8",
      "name": "",
      "type": "Shape",
      "text": "box 5",
      "master": "2",
      "geometry": {
        "BeginX": null,
        "BeginY": null,
        "EndX": null,
        "EndY": null
      },
      "line_format": {
        "LineColor": null,
        "LineWeight": "0.01041666666666667",
        "EndArrow": null
      },
      "master_nameU": "Rectangle",
      "master_name": "Rectangle",
      "master_prompt": "Drag onto the page.",
      "master_contents": {
        "shape_id": "5",
        "type": "Shape",
        "line_style": "7",
        "fill_style": "7",
        "text_style": "7",
        "cells": {
          "PinX": "1.5",
          "PinY": "1.5",
          "Width": "1",
          "Height": "-1",
          "LocPinX": "0.5",
          "LocPinY": "-0.5",
          "Angle": "0",
          "FlipX": "0",
          "FlipY": "0",
          "ResizeMode": "0",
          "BeginX": "1",
          "BeginY": "2",
          "EndX": "2",
          "EndY": "1",
          "TxtPinX": "0",
          "TxtPinY": "-1",
          "TxtWidth": "0.5555555555555556",
          "TxtHeight": "0.2444444444444444",
          "TxtLocPinX": "0.2777777777777778",
          "TxtLocPinY": "0.1222222222222222",
          "TxtAngle": "0",
          "LockHeight": "1",
          "LockCalcWH": "1",
          "HelpTopic": "Vis_SE.chm!#20000",
          "Copyright": "Copyright 2001 Microsoft Corporation.  All rights reserved.",
          "NoAlignBox": "1",
          "DynFeedback": "2",
          "GlueType": "2",
          "ObjType": "2",
          "NoLiveDynamics": "1",
          "ShapeSplittable": "1",
          "LayerMember": "0"
        },
        "sections": [
          {
            "name": "Control",
            "rows": [
              {
                "N": "TextPosition",
                "cells": {
                  "X": "0",
                  "Y": "-1",
                  "XDyn": "0",
                  "YDyn": "-1",
                  "XCon": "5",
                  "YCon": "0",
                  "CanGlue": "0",
                  "Prompt": "Reposition Text"
                }
              }
            ]
          },
          {
            "name": "Geometry",
            "rows": [
              {
                "T": "MoveTo",
                "IX": "1",
                "cells": {
                  "X": "0",
                  "Y": "0"
                }
              },
              {
                "T": "LineTo",
                "IX": "2",
                "cells": {
                  "X": "0",
                  "Y": "-1"
                }
              },
              {
                "T": "LineTo",
                "IX": "3",
                "cells": {
                  "X": "1",
                  "Y": "-1"
                }
              }
            ]
          }
        ]
      },
      "is_connector": false
    }
  ],
  "connectors": [
    {
      "id": "3",
      "name": "",
      "type": "Shape",
      "text": "",
      "master": "5",
      "geometry": {
        "BeginX": "10.4364",
        "BeginY": "5.9442",
        "EndX": "11.1112",
        "EndY": "5.9442"
      },
      "line_format": {
        "LineColor": "#000000",
        "LineWeight": "0.0278",
        "EndArrow": "4"
      },
      "master_nameU": "Dynamic connector",
      "master_name": "Dynamic connector",
      "master_prompt": "This connector automatically routes between the shapes it connects.",
      "master_contents": {},
      "is_connector": true,
      "begin_shape": "1",
      "end_shape": "2"
    },
    {
      "id": "5",
      "name": "",
      "type": "Shape",
      "text": "",
      "master": "5",
      "geometry": {
        "BeginX": "12.6112",
        "BeginY": "5.9442",
        "EndX": "13.286",
        "EndY": "5.9442"
      },
      "line_format": {
        "LineColor": "#000000",
        "LineWeight": "0.0278",
        "EndArrow": "4"
      },
      "master_nameU": "Dynamic connector",
      "master_name": "Dynamic connector",
      "master_prompt": "This connector automatically routes between the shapes it connects.",
      "master_contents": {},
      "is_connector": true,
      "begin_shape": "2",
      "end_shape": "4"
    },
    {
      "id": "7",
      "name": "",
      "type": "Shape",
      "text": "",
      "master": "5",
      "geometry": {
        "BeginX": "14.786",
        "BeginY": "5.9442",
        "EndX": "15.161",
        "EndY": "5.9442"
      },
      "line_format": {
        "LineColor": "#000000",
        "LineWeight": "0.0278",
        "EndArrow": "4"
      },
      "master_nameU": "Dynamic connector",
      "master_name": "Dynamic connector",
      "master_prompt": "This connector automatically routes between the shapes it connects.",
      "master_contents": {},
      "is_connector": true,
      "begin_shape": "4",
      "end_shape": "6"
    },
    {
      "id": "9",
      "name": "",
      "type": "Shape",
      "text": "",
      "master": "5",
      "geometry": {
        "BeginX": "16.661",
        "BeginY": "5.9442",
        "EndX": "17.036",
        "EndY": "5.9442"
      },
      "line_format": {
        "LineColor": "#000000",
        "LineWeight": "0.0278",
        "EndArrow": "4"
      },
      "master_nameU": "Dynamic connector",
      "master_name": "Dynamic connector",
      "master_prompt": "This connector automatically routes between the shapes it connects.",
      "master_contents": {},
      "is_connector": true,
      "begin_shape": "6",
      "end_shape": "8"
    }
  ]
}